filepup.net 2014-03-30

# FilePup.net - Dead Simple File Sharing!

This Privacy Policy, in conjunction with the [Terms of Service](http://www.filepup.net/help/terms.php) and other terms and conditions of use which are incorporated herein by reference and may be posted and applicable to specific services, governs your use of FilePup.net and are collectively referred to as the "Agreement". 

FilePup.net may modify the Agreement which will become effective immediately upon posting on the website. Your continued use of the website and any associated services, the "Services", indicates your acceptance of the Agreement. 

Any Content uploaded by you to FilePup.net becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy. 

FilePup.net uses IP addresses to administer the website as well as to debug errors and block offenders/attackers . 

We will not rent, sell or share your information with third parties. However, we may disclose your IP information if required by law. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. 

In the event that FilePup.net is acquired or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the information we have collected from you as part of any change of control. 

Although we strive to protect your personal information, FilePup.net cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

Please e-mail reports of any TOS violations to **support@FilePup.net**

_Last change: 03.10.2012_
